http://www.vabook.org/privacy-policy/

Bookmarks
Festival Dates:
March 13-26, 2021
Virginia Festival of the Book
ScheduleSpeakersWatchBlogGet InvolvedAbout UsPast Speakers & SchedulesPartners & SponsorsAccessibilityGive
GO
Privacy Policy
Virginia Humanities and its programs are affiliated with the University of Virginia (UVA) and are governed by and follow UVA’s Privacy Policy.
University of Virginia’s Commitment to Privacy
The University of Virginia is strongly committed to maintaining the privacy and security of confidential personal information and other highly sensitive data that it collects. Our privacy and public records obligations are governed by applicable Virginia statutes, including, but not limited to, the Virginia Privacy Protection Act of 1976, the Virginia Freedom of Information Act and by any applicable U.S. federal laws.
UVA Full Privacy Policy
Partners & Sponsors  |  View All
Never Miss A Festival Update!
Subscribe
Follow Us
A program of
Partners & Affiliates
Virginia Festival of the Book
145 Ednam Drive
Charlottesville, VA 22903
(434) 924-3296
Contact UsMedia Kit & LogosFestival PoliciesIndigenous Acknowledgement
© 2020 Virginia Humanities, All Rights Reserved •
Privacy Policy
Indigenous Acknowledgment
Virginia Humanities acknowledges the Monacan Nation, the original people of the land and waters of our home in Charlottesville, Virginia.
We invite you to learn more about Indians in Virginia in our Encyclopedia Virginia.
Explore the Virginia Humanities Network
Virginia HumanitiesVirginia Festival of the BookVirginia Center for the BookVirginia Folklife ProgramHistory UnitedVirginia Indian ArchiveEncyclopedia VirginiaDiscovery VirginiaWith Good ReasonBackStoryChanging the NarrativeAfroVirginiaFellowshipsGrants
CLOSE
